Lesson eight. Ted forms a rock band. Ted plans to become a successful musician. First,
he needs Susan to loan him money for a new guitar. Susan suggests that Ted baked cookies
to earn the money.
You're in good spirits today, Ted. I've got great news, Mom. What is it?
Amber and I are going to start a rock band. Good for you.
Mom, I'm not going to beat around the bush. I need to borrow $1,000 for a new guitar.
Ted, your father and I can't shell out that much. We aren't made of money.
You're not? I thought you were millionaires, like Donald and I've on a Trump.
Haha, this is no time to be a wise guy. I promise, I'll pay you back.
How? We're going to take the music world by storm and make lots of money.
That sounds like a pipe dream. Aren't high school rock bands a dime a dozen?
Yeah, but we're different. With my guitar playing and Amber's beautiful voice,
we're sure to make a splash. Well, we're going through hard times.
You're going to have to work for that $1,000. How?
You can bake cookies. I bet Mrs. Clapton never made Eric bake cookies.
But I guess those are the breaks.